imgtec.com 2017-05-08

# Privacy Policy - Imagination Technologies

## About Us

Imagination is a division of Imagination Technologies Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of Imagination Technologies Group plc (hereinafter referred to as “us” or “our”), a company registered in England and Wales, registration number 02920061. Our registered office and headquarters is located at Imagination House, Home Park Estate, Kings Langley, Hertfordshire WD4 8LZ.

This Privacy Policy describes the data collected by us whether:

  * on or through the websites at [ **www.imgtec.com**](https://www.imgtec.com/privacy-policy/) (the “Imagination Website”), [ **http://flow** cloud **.i** o](http://flowcloud.io/) (the “FlowCloud Website”), [**www.flowlive.com**](http://www.flowlive.com/) (the “Flow Website”) or any other of our group company websites developed or hosted by us or on our behalf (together, those websites and any that resolve to those websites shall be known as the “Websites”); or

  * in relation to our collection of any warranty registration information from a purchaser, licensee or other user of a product originally supplied by us (whether or not through the Websites) (“Product”); or

  * in relation to the registration of details concerning retailers and staff of retailers who have sold Products; or
  * in relation to information you may give us about you by filling in forms on our any of our Websites or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our Website, subscribe to our service, submit information to or search for information on our Website and when you report a problem with our Website. We do not assume any liability for any information that you submit or provide to us (whether or not such information relates to you or to someone else). You hereby expressly represent and warrant to us that you have all necessary rights and/or have obtained all necessary approvals, permissions and consents required by applicable law to submit or provide such information.

In this Privacy Policy, references to “you” means any person submitting any data to us or to the Websites about himself or herself or about any other living individual in respect of any use of the Websites or the services available through the Websites (the “Services”) or the obtaining or supply of the Product.

This Privacy Policy sets out the ways in which we may use your information.

If you have any questions, comments or suggestions about the way in which we use your personal information or if any of your personal information changes, please write to us at the above address or email us at [ **webmaster@imgtec.com**](mailto:webmaster@imgtec.com).

Your privacy is very important to you and us. We shall therefore only use your name and other information which relates to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We will only use your personal information in a way that is fair to you. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant to our dealings with you.

We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law, or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

### Data that we collect and our use of it

#### 1\. Developer Portals

When you and other developers participate in technical discussions and provide Product feedback on Websites such as our PowerVR Insider Forum on the Imagination Website, we collect and analyse the discussions, review feedback on our Products and store the information you provide upon registration. We may use that information for internal purposes to update our Products, design and develop new products and services, analyse the use of our Websites, respond to your queries, allow you to access certain restricted areas on our Websites and to provide you with information and updates regarding our Products. By posting any information on any of our discussion forums you are disclaiming all intellectual property and moral rights in and to the content of your submissions and you acknowledge that we can use the information posted by you in any manner we see fit.

#### 2\. Product Warranty Registrations

When you register a warranty for a new Product that you have received, we may receive the following information about you: your name, date of birth, address, email address, telephone numbers, Product details, serial number for the Product, where you obtained the Product, the date on which you obtained the Product, why you bought the Product and what you are considering buying next. We need that information to verify that you are entitled to receive a warranty, and to verify the dates on which your warranty is applicable. We may use that information when carrying out any servicing or repairs to the Product that you have obtained, and we may also pass that information on to anyone carrying out servicing or repairs on our behalf. We may also use your information in case we have marketing messages, upgrade, safety or recall reasons and any other queries. If there is a free prize draw for any warranty cards supplied by us, we may also use that information for the purposes of entering you in the draw, and we may also use the information in the ways described in the section below relating to promotions.

#### 3\. Promotions

When you enter a promotion (such as a free prize draw) run by us or if you are a winner of the promotion, you may supply various information about yourself or someone else, or we may receive or gather information supplied about you. For example, the information we may collect may include your name, date of birth, email address, telephone numbers, address, photograph, whether and how you are connected with us, information about Products (including, but not limited to, serial number, purchased from, purchase/sale date, reason for buying the radio, what you are thinking of buying next) and Services and software we supply, how you heard about us or the Product or the Services or the Websites, and your use of the Product or Services. If you participate in a retailer prize draw, your employer or manager’s details. Some of this information is for the purpose of entering the promotion and for validating your entry. We may also use that information for the purposes of informing you and sending you a prize if you are a winner, and for publicising the details of the winners of our promotions on the Websites and in our marketing materials. We may also use your information in case we have any queries.

#### 4\. The Flow Websites

We collect various types of information from you when you use the FlowCloud and/or Flow Websites. This may include your name, email address, password, security question and answer, address, telephone numbers, gender and date of birth. This information is for all customised use of these Websites, including so you can log-in, save your favourites and make your experience of these Websites personal to you to customise your settings in a way that suits you.

The information you provide may also include details of any Product (including serial number, date of purchase, place of purchase, whether you listened to the product in store, your views of your shopping experience, your comments on the Product, where you heard about the Product, and where you use your Product). This information is to enable you to link your Product to the Service provided through the Websites.

### Other uses of your personal information

We may use information that you provide to us or that we collect about you (which may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, personal description and photograph) to enable you to use other of our Websites and/or other parts of the Websites, for us to detect any fraud or abuses of the Websites, for us to send you information relevant to the Product, Services or Websites for which you have subscribed, in case there is any servicing required, to improve the Websites and our Services and Products, and in case we have any queries.

We may also use your email address that you initially give to us to enable you to commence using the Services and to validate information you have given to us. If you are a winner of a promotion (such as a free prize draw), we may display some information about you on the Websites or in our other marketing materials, but we shall not be responsible if any third party misuses that information.

We may use your contact details to respond to you any queries you raise with us.  
We may email you with your password if you tell us or the Websites that you have forgotten it.  
We may also use your data to send you feedback forms to complete about us or our Products or Services, and to contact you over any aspect of the Products or Services or the Websites.

By publishing your data on the Websites or our promotional and marketing material, this information may be accessible internationally including in countries outside the European Economic Area. Some places outside of the EEA may not have adequate data protection laws at all or may offer differing levels of protection of personal information which are not as high as in the UK. By submitting your data (or allowing your data to be submitted) to us or to the Websites, you acknowledge that provided we have used your data in the ways set out in this Privacy Policy, we cannot be held responsible for any use of your data by third parties who receive and process your data.

We use your password to allow you to use restricted parts of the Websites. We use that to enable you or anyone you represent or who represents you to access your restricted parts on the Websites.  
You must only submit to us or the Websites information which is accurate and not misleading and you must keep it up to date and inform us of changes. By submitting information about you or anyone else, you must ensure that you have full authority and consent to supply us with that information on everyone’s behalf and you warrant to us that you have that authority.

### Third Parties and Links

We may pass information about you or your Products to anyone carrying out servicing or repairs on our behalf.

If you take part in a promotion, we may pass on your details to anyone who administers the distribution or redemption of prizes.

We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in our Privacy Policy.  
For example, we may use third parties to assist us with providing the administration for running the Websites or providing the Services, to analyse data and to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance.

We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and  
credit risk reduction.

We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business  
or part of it.

We may also disclose your details as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law.

The Websites may contain advertising of third parties, dedicated pages operated by third parties and links to other Websites or frames of other Websites (including links to access radio stations operated by third parties). Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those third parties or other websites or services, nor for any third party to whom we transfer your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

### Generic Data

We may aggregate and anonymise data relating to you so that the aggregated and anonymised data does not identify you or any individual personally. We may supply that aggregated and anonymised data to any third party without recourse to you or any other user.

### Security

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorised access and accidental loss of your data.

We store your personal details on a secure server. We use industry standard security and firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Website Certificate technology. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details.

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity, for example, your password, before we disclose personal information to you.  
You are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer.

### Cookie Policy

The Websites use cookies to collect information. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer or other mobile or handheld device (such as smart ‘phones or ‘tablets’) as you browse the Websites. They are used to ‘remember’ when your computer or device accesses the Website. The cookies are essential to the effective operation of our Websites and to enable to you navigate and use the Websites and shop with us online. Cookies are also used to tailor the Products and services offered and advertised to our customers, both on the Websites and elsewhere.

If you want to find out more information about cookies, please go to[ **  cookies**](https://www.imgtec.com/cookies/)[ **.**](https://www.imgtec.com/cookies)

### Your Rights

We may also use the information that we collect about you or that you provide to us to send you other information about us, our Products and Services and software (including upgrades), our sales promotions, our newsletters, anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners in which we believe you may be interested. If you would prefer not to receive any of this additional information as detailed in this paragraph (or any part of it) please send us an appropriate email to webmaster@imgtec.com or write to us at the above address specifying which information you do not wish to receive. Within 28 working days of receipt of your instruction we will cease to send you information as requested. If your instruction is not clear, we will cease to send you all information referred to in this paragraph. If you opt-out of receiving further information from us, we may also not enter you in a free prize draw or other promotion.

You the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Changes

Any material changes to the way in which we use your data will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. Each time you use the Websites or submit personal information to us or the Websites, you agree that the Privacy Policy current at that time shall apply to all information which we hold about you.

### Consent

By submitting data to us and using the Websites, you consent to our use of your data and of your party in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy (as amended) and you are responsible for ensuring that you have authority to consent on behalf of anyone about whom you submit data.

For any enquiry about our privacy policy please address our [ **Webmaster**](mailto:webmaster@imgtec.com).
